http://www.greenspanai.com/privacy-policy/

California Wildfire & Smoke Damage Claim Management Assistance - Click Here
×
Logo
The Greenspan Co. Privacy Policy
General StatementWe recognize and respect the privacy expectations of our clients, and have adopted this privacy policy in recognition of our obligations under the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act.If you have questions about, or you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, please contact us. This policy applies to current and former clients of our firm.Recognition of Customer Privacy ExpectationsThe Greenspan Co./Adjusters International does not disclose any nonpublic, personal information about our clients or former clients to affiliates or nonaffiliated third parties except under limited circumstances as permitted by law. We will not disclose such information in the future, except as permitted by law.What Private Information We CollectThe firm collects limited nonpublic, personal information about you in the course of providing public adjusting services on your behalf. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.This information may include your name and other related general financial information like your employment status, Social Security Number, bank account information, financial and other information about your real and personal property, and other data collected during the course of our relationship. You may contact us via telephone or email at any time to see what data we have about you, and you may change, correct, delete or express any concerns you may have about the use of your data.Limiting Employee AccessThe privacy of client information is the responsibility of every employee of The Greenspan Co./Adjusters International.We restrict access to a client’s nonpublic personal information to those employees who need to know that information to provide our adjusting services on your behalf. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard nonpublic personal information.We only disclose your personal information to the extent necessary to obtain the best settlement for you.Sincerely,THE GREENSPAN CO./ADJUSTERS INTERNATIONAL
Wildfire Assistance From a Client's Perspective
Click here for a client letter explaining their experience and insights.
